swapalease.com 2011-11-12

# Swapalease.com Worlds Largest Lease Marketplace

## SWAPALEASE INC. PRIVACY STATEMENT LAST UPDATED: 09/29/2010

Swapalease Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.swapalease.com of Swapalease Inc.'s Website. 

TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this web site has agreed to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site
  2. The organization collecting the information
  3. How the information is used
  4. With whom the information may be shared
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Swapalease Inc. control
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact Scot Hall, of the Swapalease Client Services Department by emailing Mr. Hall at shall@swapalease.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. 

### Information Collection and Use

Swapalease Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Swapalease Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

### Registration

General Perspective:

It is not necessary for a user to register in order to browse the Swapalease Inc. Web Site; however, it is recommended so that the staff at Swapalease Inc. can keep users posted of new listings and special events. It will also allow personalization of the web site when the user returns in the future. 

Lease "Seller's" Perspective:

In order to list a leased vehicle on this website, a user must first complete the required listing sections. During registration a user is required to provide sensitive information (such as credit card number including expiration date), in addition to contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code). This information is principally used for listing advertisement purposes and the collection of any listing fee due Swapalease Inc.. Secondarily, this data is used for contacting the user as well as making the sight more personalized for a particular user. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Swapalease uses cookies to enhance the users experience on the site and to track user behavior while visiting the site. 

If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We do collect log files pertaining to domain names, access times, pages visited, and browser type. These files are not linked to personally identifiable information and are only used for the sole purpose of site management. 

### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

For users completing the "Publisher Application", a 3rd party, Commission Junction Inc. is collecting user data and storing this information outside of the Swapalease website. 

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Swapalease Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. If these surveys or contests are administered by a 3rd party, the information you provide will be given to the 3rd party. This information will not be used for marketing or contacting you outside of the Swapalease system by any 3rd parties. You may contact Swapalease at 1-866-SWAPNOW (1-866-792-7669) if you do not wish to have your information given to 3rd parties. 

### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link [www.verisign.com](http://www.verisign.com/). 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must reenter their password to regain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [security@swapalease.com](mailto:security@swapalease.com). 

### Supplementation of Information

In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it may be necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. 

For example, to determine if our customers qualify (meet generally accepted leasing company credit standards) for lease transfers it may be necessary for us to use their name and social security number to request a credit report. Once we determine a user's creditworthiness, this document is handled in a matter consistent with Fair Credit Reporting Act guidelines. 

### Special Offers

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. 

### Site and Service Updates

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone. 

### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. One way this can be accomplished is at the "Managing Your Account" page after member log in. Other avenues include emailing, phoning, or standard mailing our customer support site (see "Contact Us" page for detailed information). 

### Choice/Opt-out

Our users are notified of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive our memorandums or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at [support@swapalease.com](mailto:support@swapalease.com). 

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

### Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Swapalease Inc. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at [support@swapalease.com](mailto:support@swapalease.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

### Swapalease Inc. Blog

If you use the Swapalease Inc. Blog on this Web site, you should be aware than any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage 30 days prior to making the changes so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

| |   
---|---|---  
| 

## Third Party Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy applies to the use of the software BTBUCKETS MANAGER, owned by BTBUCKETS. 

This Privacy Policy was prepared to warn you (user) about the information we collect when you visit websites that use the software supplied by BTBUCKETS. We clarify that the websites that use our software are obliged, according to our instrument of license, to maintain a non-disclosure policy in line with current market practices, inform its users about the use of the BTBUCKETS software and how to proceed so that users may “OPT-OUT” from the collection of browsing information through the BTBUCKETS software.

By accessing or using the websites that use the BTBUCKETS software, you will be automatically authorizing the use of your data according to our Non-Disclosure Policy. If you do not approve the capture, use and/or disclosure of your data, as described herein, you shall “OPT-OUT”.

BTBUCKETS acknowledges that the non-disclosure policy is very important

****WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT****

BTBUCKETS has conceived and developed the BTBUCKETS MANAGER software, which function, generally, is to group users with similar browsing characteristics, and analyze their behavior on the Internet. 

Thus, the Software BTBUCKETS MANAGER will gather data while you are visiting the websites that use the Software of BTBUCKETS. This data includes information designated by the owner of the website, such as IP address, Web pages examined by you, date and time, domain type, among other browsing information and preferences. BTBUCKETS may use different types of technologies to collect this type of information, including “cookies”. 

Websites that are using BTBUCKETS MANAGER are required to not collect personal identifiable information (PII) , which may lead to identification of the user who visits this website. 

The user may decide to not permit that BTBUCKETS use its anonymous data through the Opt-Out procedure (“dispose of”), namely “withdraw my data from his database completely.” For this [click HERE](http://btbuckets.com/site/optout). 

BTBUCKETS will use your non-personal information to analyze your behavior on the Internet, grouping it with other users who have similar browsing characteristics to your own. BTBUCKETS will segment the exhibition of contents with items that seem to be of interest to a certain group.

**Certain browsing aspects in this website:**

**Cookies:** A “cookie” is a fragment of information kept in the user’s computer, connected to his information. BTBUCKETS can use “cookies” (information sent by the server of BTBUCKETS to your computer, with the objective of identifying it). We use the cookies to store the preferences of users and follow up on trends. 

We clarify that the majority of browsers are configured to accept cookies, but you can redefine your browser to reject all the cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some resources and services of BTBUCKETS may not work correctly if the cookies are disabled.

**Registration Information:** When you access websites that use the Software, BTBUCKETS automatically records on its servers the information that you sent through your browser while visiting the site. ****

******Communication with the user:** When you send an e-mail or other communication to the website of BTBUCKETS, we can retain these communications to process your requests and improve our services. BTBUCKETS reserves itself the right to select the content to be posted in the forum of the website. ****

Other sites: This site contains links to external sites, whose non-disclosure policies are not the responsibility of BTBUCKETS.

**INFORMATION SHARING**

By accessing the websites that use the BTBUCKETS Software, you are automatically authorizing the sharing of your anonymous behavioral data with BTBuckets and the site with Software installed. If you do not approve the capture, the use and disclosure your anonymous behavioral data, as described herein, use of the [Opt-Out tool](http://btbuckets.com/site/optout).

When we need third parties to help process your information, we request that they comply with our Non-Disclosure policy and other appropriate safety and non-disclosure measures.

**SAFETY OF INFORMATION**

BTBUCKETS uses commercially reasonable physical, administrative and technical protections to preserve the integrity and safety of your information. We cannot, however, assure or guarantee the safety of any information that you transmit to specific media. Therefore, you so do at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, BTBUCKETS makes commercially reasonable endeavors to ensure the safety of our systems. However, please observe that this is not a guarantee that such information cannot be accessed, revealed, altered or destroyed by violation of our physical, technical or administrative protections. 

**INTEGRITY OF DATA**

BTBUCKETS processes your information only for the purposes proposed and according to the Policy or any notice of non-disclosure of a specific applicable service. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process information with the objective of grouping users with similar browsing characteristics.

**PROPERTY RIGHTS**

The intellectual property rights of the BTBUCKETS software, including its content, applications and systems, belong to BTBUCKETS, (ii) are licensed to the websites registered in the service and/or (iii) are free to use. 

It is expressly prohibited to market, reproduce, modify, download, publish or distribute, at any title and in any way, the technical material and other contents existing in this website and in the Portal, without previous authorization from BTBUCKETS or third parties. 

The right of use over the information contained in the website does not guarantee to the User the right to use any trademarks, logos, domain names, business names and any other distinctive signs of BTBUCKETS and/or of partners exposed in the website and in the Portal. 

The User agrees that he will not remove, obscure or alter any information or content of the website. Commercial exploitation by third parties of the website’s content is expressly prohibited. 

**CHANGES**

**** The services available in the website may be modified, substituted or excluded without the User having any right or indemnity resulting from said change, amendment, substitution or exclusion. 

This Policy may also be altered, and these alterations will come into effect at the time they are published in the website. Continuous use by the User after insertion of the alterations in this Policy will consist in consent by the User with such Non-Disclosure policy of the website of BTBUCKETS. 

******ALTERATIONS IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy may be altered periodically and without notice. BTBUCKETS may alter the Privacy Policy at any time, publishing the alterations on this page. Date presented below (YEAR-MONTH-DAY) reflects latest updates to this policy.

LAST UPDATE: 2009-07-13

|   
| |   
  
### Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
Phone: 1-866-SWAPNOW (1-866-792-7669)  
Fax: (513) 381-1091  
Email: [support@swapalease.com](mailto:support@swapalease.com)  
Postal Address: 

11224 Cornell Park Drive  
Cincinnati, Ohio 45242
